It came to light that people had
not insured their vehicles because many
people say that if the vehicle
is not in use then what is the use of insuring it.
Keeping this issue in mind,
ICICI Lombard has launched Mostly policy in
which people can
insure their vehicle only when they
use it. In this regard, today
ICICI Uma held a press conference and told the
media that to address the
insurance retirement of surprise,
we are
launching retiring products. So, in all these
products, the basic needs like
customer care, the changes that have taken place,
no doctor consultation
or whatever, were not there, but today,
using technology, ICICI
Lombard is launching new products by adding such features
that the customer will be able to do everything
sitting idle. At the
time of reading today, 2 years ago, when the customer
kept his two wheeler or four wheeler at home, it was
not insured because he was not able to drive it. Right then, a
new
retirement came in the customer started thinking that if
I keep this car outside, then brother.  If I am not going out then pay
it on insurance, so something like this can happen
where if I do it then I pay, so
keeping this in mind we are
launching motor policy where we
say, so
nowadays we know that to grow and
promote medium oil enterprises,
many of
you, ICICI Lombard has also come in the general insurance sector,
we must have
taken a portal for them, so the small businesses that are
running can
cover their risk in a very good way by using their products,
so this is the thing that we want to tell you all,
that is why we have
gathered here today, thank you, thank you.